augustasportswear.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy

Effective August 1, 2016 

Augusta Sportswear, Inc. is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our Web site and users of the other services available through our site. We will use our best efforts to ensure that all information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein. 

**What information do we collect?** We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. 

**What do we use your information for?** Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

-To personalize your experience -your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
-To improve our website- we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
-To improve customer service- your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
-To process transactions - your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
-To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
-To send periodic emails which may include emails from our related companies.

The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**How do we protect your information?** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. When we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

**Tracking Technologies/Cookies -** Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.   
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect others or ours rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Your Choices For Controlling Your Information/Opting Out -** We are concerned about the accuracy, currency and completeness of the information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update or delete personally identifiable information we have collected about you online, contact us at : 1-800-237-6695. We will respond to your access request within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated. You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your personal information from our visitor records by sending an email to sales@augustasportswear.com. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any commercial purpose. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to any of the sites blocked. 

**Third party links -** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance -** We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older. 

**Your Consent -** By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy -** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will advise you of those changes and also post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us -** If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at sales@augustasportswear.com or 800.237.6695
